https://www.premierworkspaces.com/privacy-policy

Seattle
Washington D.C.
Washington D.C.
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Privacy Policy applies to the www.premierworkspaces.com website and Premier Office Centers, LLC dba Premier Workspaces (“Premier”) and governs data collection and usage. The Premier website is an Information, Products and Services site. Premier’s website may provide links to third party websites for your convenience and information. Premier does not control third party sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our own privacy practices. This Privacy Policy does not cover any personal data that you choose to give to unrelated third parties.
Collection of your Personal Information
When browsing on the website, you are not required to provide any personal information. If you choose to register with Premier, then you will be requested to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Premier's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Premier. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Premier website.
Premier encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Premier so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Premier is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Premier website.
Use of Personal Information
Premier collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. Premier does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties. Premier may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Premier and its affiliates. Premier may also, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Premier may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Premier, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. If you do not want to receive this these additional communications, you may opt-out (see the Opt-Out section below).
Premier may contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Premier may also keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Premier, in order to determine what Premier services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Premier to users whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Premier will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Premier or the website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Premier; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Premier or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Premier website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Premier website or other websites you visit.
Security of Personal Information
The security of your personal information is very important to us; however, no security system is guaranteed to be totally secure. While Premier makes every effort to protect your personal information, Premier cannot guarantee or warrant the security of our servers or that information you supply will not be intercepted. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. Premier uses VeriSign Secure Site Services to provide VeriSign SSL Certificates. VeriSign is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. VeriSign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity, and intellectual property.
Children Under Thirteen
Premier does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information.
Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Premier by contacting us here:
Web page: www.premierworkspaces.com
Email: info@premierworkspaces.com
Phone: (877) 697-8483
Changes to this Statement
Premier will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Premier encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Premier is protecting your information.
Terms and Conditions
If you visit Premier websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including, but not limited to, disclaimers of warranty, limitations of liability, and application of the law of the State of California.
Contact Information
Premier welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Premier has not adhered to this policy, please contact Premier at:
Premier Workspaces2102 Business Center Drive Irvine, California 92612
Washington D.C.
